♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
All right, let's go!
♪ Cambot ♪
Pan left!
♪ Gypsy ♪
Hi, girl!
♪ Tom Servo ♪
What a cool guy!
♪ Croooow ♪
He's a wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show, ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar twang)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Hi everybody, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
Uh, we'll be right back.
- Don't, no, don't Joel, no.
We're not starting yet.
(sneezing)
- Bless you.
- [Magic Voice] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
(sneezing)
- Oh, gross.
- Oh Crow, here,
you got a little...
Here, blow.
- Hey, aqualung.
(blowing nose)
- Okay.
A little more, blow harder.
- [Magic Voice] Commercial
sign in five, four, three, two.
Commercial sign now.
(coughing)
(sneezing)
- Oh, we'll be right back.
(instrumental theme music)
(groaning)
- Oh, much better.
Whoa.
- Wow, yeah.
- Vapor action.
- It really works.
- Yeah, I feel great.
Hey, what'd you put in
that vapor stuff anyway?
- This says tetrahydrozoline,
sodium T-laurel sulfate,
UB40, FD&C Red 40, Simply Red,
flavor, magnesium
silicate, a flowing agent,
BHT to preserve
flavor, and Spacom.
It says may cause drowsiness,
do not operate heavy machinery.
- Uh Joel, we are
heavy machinery, buddy.
(laughing)
Cool, huh?
- Good one.
It says it may cause flashbacks.
- Hey Joel, the mad
scientists are calling.
- Uh-oh.
- He says, "That
was number five!"
(laughing)
Oh, hello Joel.
Yard Ape here suggested you
go first on the
Invention Exchange.
Have at it, space guy.
(laughing)
- Whoo!
- Ouch, jeepers.
Well, my invention this
week is for sign language.
I don't know sign language,
so I invented this device.
It's a translator,
you speak into one end
and it does international
sign language on the other.
Let me show you what I mean.
Okay, let's do something simple.
I.
See?
Love.
You.
See how that works?
- Aww, that's really sweet.
- That's great.
- And I also can do, I'd
like to do a little joke
for our friends who use sign
language who watch the show.
That's a number five!
(chuckling)
It is kinda neat.
You can do a lot of
other things with it too,
like it's a hearing aid.
Hearing aid.
(groaning)
Voice amplifier.
Voice amplify.
(chuckling)
And visor.
- Huh, neat.
- See, pretty neat huh?
What do ya think, sirs?
Straighten up.
- What?
Your movie today, Joel, is--
- A biker film?
- Biker film.
Hey, how did you know that?
- Well, you're on bikes,
I just sorta guessed.
- No!
= No!
- What are we saying no for?
- I thought you knew.
- I was following
your lead, mamajamma.
- Oh, well, send 'em
the movie then, Frank.
- I don't fink on soul brother.
(alarms blaring)
- Ooh, movie sign!
(mechanical whirring)
- [Joel] I wonder why they
didn't bury him in a sidecar,
you know, they're bikers.
- [Tom] Look, there's Yasser
Arafat in his teen days.
- [Joel] Walk like
an Egyptian, man.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] Hair color
by Bozo the Clown.
- [Tom] Jackets from the
Sonny Bono Collection.
(Crow laughing)
- [Crow] Hey,
here's a good space.
- [Tom] I think this is the
day the music died, guys.
Kinda late with that
coat, aren't ya?
[Joel] Where were they
when they needed it?
When he needed the coat.
- [Crow] Now, how much would
you pay for this
Ginsu switchblade?
Wait, there's more.
You get the bread knife,
the Uzi automatic,
the love beads, a pair of
gloves, some guy's keys.
You know, professional
low-life scum
would pay $9.99 for this stuff.
But wait, there's more.
You also get this
foxy biker chick's...
Ginsu bra snappler.
- [Tom] That thing is huge.
- [Tom] What's goin' on?
- [Crow] Where's she going?
- Are you ready for that?
- Yeah.
I wonder if those slobs would
be as gentle with that box
if they know that their
dearly departed leader inside
was about to ratfink on 'em.
- [Tom] Huh?
- Yeah, it's too
bad Adrian got wise
just as we were
getting close to him.
- [Joel] What is this,
Sergeant Exposition
and Detective Plot Point?
- Well, don't worry.
One of these days he's
gonna stretch things
just a little too
wide, and then--
- [Joel] I open my eyes.
- Well, we've been after him
for about six months now.
- Nope, we'll get him.
- [Tom] Uh, he's dead.
Isn't he?
- We'll get them too.
- [Crow] Hey, Ted Bessel's
got nothin' on that guy.
- Mr. Adrian, did you notice
who came to join the party?
- Chapman.
- [Joel] Tracy Chapman?
- How could I miss him?
For the past six months,
he's been like my shadow.
- [Crow] But not as chunky.
- I think the next funeral
we attend might be his.
- [Crow] Hey, the
film guide said
that that guy is the director.
- The next pick-up's
tomorrow at Scorpio's.
- [Tom] Tell Scorpio
to use his code name.
(motorcycles revving)
Bye, teen gang.
- Man, what are we gonna do
now that Big Daddy's snuffed?
- [Tom] Ah, use slang
as much as we can.
- We got us a new leader.
- [Joel] Huh?
- Yeah, man?
- [Joel] Lee Iacocca?
- Me, baby.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- Me.
- [Joel] Sorry I
brought it up, jeepers.
Huh?
- [Tom] Meanwhile,
in outer space.
- [Joel] Movie Cops presents!
- [Tom] Gemini.
(funky music)
- [Crow] Anthony
Cardoza, featuring rich
Corinthian leather.
- [Tom] Backgrounds illustrated
with a Technicolor yawn.
♪ Hellcats parading
down the street ♪
- [Joel] Wow,
they're really mean
but they've got a
great theme song.
- [Tom] Oh no, Ross Hagen!
Chili peppers, they burn my gut.
♪ Don't mess around ♪
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Joel] Six Pack, that
must be a biker, huh?
- [Tom] Nah, that's
his Christian name.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Crow] Hey, Bro Beck.
Hope he plays Take Five.
- [Tom] Candy Cave and her
Romanian cousin,
Sucrose Spelunker.
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Huh?
- [Tom] Looks like a
Rorschach test doesn't it?
What so you see?
- [Joel] Uh, I see
a dismal film ahead.
- [Tom] Yep, yep.
- [Crow] You know,
it kinda looks like
Jackson Pollock did the
background paintings.
- [Tom] Yeah, after
the car accident.
- [Crow] Hey, Gus Trichonosis,
in charge of undercooked pork.
- [Joel] Huh?
- [Tom] Scab?
How do you suppose
they picked him?
(laughing)
- [Joel] Hey.
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Crow] Hey, Davy Jones!
Before the Monkees.
- [Joel] Oh, no it's not.
- [Crow] Yes it is!
- [Joel] No.
- [Crow] It was
before the Monkees.
- [Joel] He would
have been about 14,
he spelled his name
completely different.
- [Crow] I'll bet, I'll bet.
- [Joel] No way, femmebot.
- [Crow] Oh yes
way, space swish.
- [Joel] Hey, I'm gonna
shut you down, Buckwheat.
- [Crow] Ah, shut down this.
- [Tom] Shut up, you two!
Come on.
- [Crow] Hey look, children
is spelled wrong too.
That proves my point.
- [Joel] No it doesn't!
- [Crow] Yes it does.
- [Tom] Oh...
- [Joel] No it doesn't.
- [Crow] Does too.
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Tom] Oh look,
there's Tony Houston,
you know what he wrote?
He wrote Sidehackers too.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Tom] Yeah.
Yuck.
- [Joel] Houston,
Huggs, Prince and Hong.
Which one of these
doesn't belong?
- [Tom] They're cops.
- [Crow] Hey, Eric Lindberg,
he flew from New York to Paris.
- [Joel] Would you shut up?
♪ Shocking everyone they meet ♪
- [Crow] Motorcycles
by Ford Puckett,
Kirby Puckett's brother.
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Just stop.
- [Crow] Hey Bill,
your rear's done.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Ah jeez, that's
cool, I can dig that.
♪ Hellcats, parading
down the street ♪
- [Joel] Even if we disagree,
it's all in good-natured
fun isn't it?
- [Tom] Yeah, it sure is.
- [Crow] Cemetery
furnishings by Jiffy Tomb.
- [Tom] Negative cutter,
he says "Oh, I hate my job.
"Everything about it is bad."
♪ Don't mess around ♪
- [Crow] Author of
the Kinzie report.
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Crow] Fine
Corinthian leather.
- [Tom] Cordoza.
(chuckling)
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Joel] Oh, if this is
a Slatzer film, it
might get really bloody.
- [Crow] That's slasher.
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Tom] Scenic Love Canal.
(engine revving)
- [Joel] Wow.
(funky music)
- [Tom] Hey, they're playing
The Girl from Ipanema here.
- [Joel] Long and cool
and tan and lovely,
the boy from
Ipanema goes biking,
and when he bikes, all the guys
on their motor trikes go "Ah."
- [Tom] Hellcats, terrorizing
the desolate wastelands
for over half a century.
Man welded to machine.
- [Crow] Hey, fancy
meeting you here.
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Hmm, still a bike.
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] Here's
your modeling clay.
I made a bunny.
- [Tom] Oh, smart.
They're in the
middle of nowhere,
but they make their drug
deal out in the open
by the side of the road
while a car passes by!
- [Joel] Why do you
think they call it dope?
(engines revving)
- [Crow] Remember, we
got bridge club at 4:00.
- [Joel] Yep.
Yeah, this thing'll...
I get on this and
the wheels...
- [Tom] I know this wiener dude,
he sells this wiener food.
He gives me everything from
tire irons on down, hey.
I'd like to split his head
open with a tire iron.
Heh, I made that up myself.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Crow] That's great.
(chuckling)
Hey, his two-cycle's got some
real knocking and
pinging problems.
- [Tom] Now I just turn
right at the slag heap.
- [Joel] Yeah.
Must be on the way home.
Yeah, looks like
nice digs, you know.
It's not much, but
it's centrally located.
No kids cutting across
the lawn or anything.
Hey old lady, I'm home.
- You been on a
tour or something?
I've been waiting here
for over two hours
and Adrian's gonna
be madder than hell.
- [Tom] Oooh.
- Here's the money I made.
Snake was late
running in from Mexico
and I couldn't
afford to get caught
with that powder in my pocket.
- [Crow] (chuckling)
Nice read, Richards.
- [Joel] I'm a stranger
to my own soul.
(engine starting)
Listen, there's a
dance next Friday
and I was thinking maybe--
Oh, forget it.
- [Tom] Wonder if
she got her bra back.
- [Crow] Hey, I
remember her now.
She was the star of
Then Came Bronson.
- [Joel] That was a guy.
- [Crow] No it wasn't
- [Joel] It was too.
- [Crow] Was not.
- [Tom] Was Not Was, there.
I made a meaningless
pop culture reference,
now knock it off!
- [Crow] Well where's
she going anyway?
- [Joel] I don't know,
nowhere in particular.
- [Crow] Man, I sure envy her.
- [Joel] Yeah
well, take it easy.
- [Tom] For those of you
playing along at home,
Joel and Crow just
reenacted the opening scene
of Then Came Bronson.
We'll be right back.
(laughing)
- You're late.
- [Tom] Don Fido is mad.
- I don't like waiting.
What do you hear from the
good Detective Chapman?
- He's got us up tight.
- In that case, we'll
have to loosen things up.
(loud music chord)
- [Joel] I'm the director,
I make the music
louder when it's on me.
- [Crow] All done?
Shep, some day this
will all be yours.
- [Tom] What a neat bunch.
We'll be right back.
(instrumental theme music)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Meanwhile on Route 66,
James Dean takes a lazy spin.
- [Tom] What's in store for
these two lamebrains here?
- [Crow] I said I'm pregnant!
- [Tom] Oh, I just love
this Charles Ives music.
Got any Ralph Vaughan Williams?
- [Joel] It's me, the director
again, I use my talents.
- [Tom] Tony Houston,
co-writer and AD.
I got the dry look.
- [Crow] Let's park the
Barbiemobile right here.
- [Tom] Let's part the
Gangstermobile right here.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] I need it now.
- [Tom] Now, now!
- [Crow] Hmm?
Hey, Bob.
That's me up there.
(soft music)
- [Joel] Take my hand, I'm
a stranger in paradise.
[Crow] She's wearing a
Sunkist promotional pantsuit.
Must be one of the gold diggers.
- [Tom] Oh boy,
what a tough lie.
I'm glad I brought my light bag.
I was playing a Wilson four.
- [Crow] Steve has a problem.
His problem is down there.
Now he must tell Eliza.
- Tell me.
- [Joel] I was in Guam
and they stuck bamboo
under my nails, all right?
- You broke your promise.
Quote, "Let's take a long
drive in the country."
- [All] Unquote.
- "Maybe the fresh air
will clear my head.
"I'm beginning to feel more
like a junkie than a narco cop."
- [Joel] You're not
supposed to take them,
just confiscate 'em.
- Yellow jackets,
reds, bennies, H.
- Look--
- [Crow] Why do you think
they call it exposition?
- With a cigarette?
- They're in the car.
- [Tom] Hey, he's the guy from
the beginning of the film,
Detective Plot Point.
- What I go through.
- [Tom] D'oh.
- [Joel] And get me a slug from
a thirty-aught-six
when you're up.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Hey...
Hey, I remember this from
The Day of the Jackal, guys.
- [Crow] And now, Red
in the silent spot.
Red plays a guy about
to get gunned down.
Let's watch.
- [Joel] Found this in
a warehouse in Dallas,
I hope it works.
- [Tom] You gettin'
this, Zapruder?
There.
(gun fires)
Huh?
- [Crow] Oh, that
sounds like Steve
taking a slug from
a thirty-aught-six.
- [Tom] Steve's dead now.
From here on in, Steve's death
will be represented by the oboe.
- [Joel] Oh, what a time to
dress wrong for a slaying.
- [Tom] It's not like
Steve to run off and die.
(screaming)
- No!
- [Joel] My seat covers!
(screaming)
- [Tom] Nice screams.
- [Crow] Meanwhile,
in Gordon Gekko's jet.
(grunting)
- [Joel] Ah, so
that's how it works.
All right.
- [Tom] Ross Hagen! (groaning)
- [Joel] Oh man.
Captain Ross Hagen to you, pal.
- Thanks for the ride.
- We owe you much
more than a ride, son.
- [Crow] You're a way of life.
- [Joel] Hey Steve, mind if we
get in on some of that action?
- Senator Carter,
Senator Linfield,
this is my brother's
fiancee, Linda Martin.
- My pleasure, Ms. Martin.
- [Crow] Ah, so she's available?
- Sergeant Chapman
told us what happened.
You have the deepest
sympathy of both myself and--
- [Joel] The entire human
race, including red China.
- [Crow] Thanks for the jet.
- [Joel] You know,
these are great lyrics.
You've got real talent!
- That's it, all Dave
had was the notebook.
- No names, no faces,
you never saw anyone.
- [Tom] Just
elbows, it was dark.
- Hellcats.
(Tom humming theme song)
- I wonder.
- [Linda] What?
- [Crow] Who wrote
the book of love?
- If you hunt them
like you hunt people.
- [Joel] Yeah, you kinda do.
Dig a two-foot hole,
put Crisco in--
Oh, that's bears.
- [Crow] Uh, that's the closet.
- What are you planning to do?
- [Joel] Catch a
show at the Copa.
Whenever a brother dies,
they fly me in for free.
I like to take advantage.
- [Crow] Uh, Ross, you're
wearing her purse on your head.
- [Tom] I dare you to knock
this battery off my shoulder.
Go ahead, I dare ya.
- [Joel] Utah, I can't
believe I'm still in Utah.
I'm filled with shame, I am.
(engine revving)
- [Crow] Then came moron.
(squeaking)
(indistinct singing)
- [Tom] Great song, huh?
Hi, I'm Shelly. (giggling)
Rub my belly.
- [Crow] Today's tough
but tender youth,
driving the big steamers
across this great land.
- [Tom] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Filmed in Zapruder-vision, guys.
(imitating singer)
- [Joel] Innuendo freeway.
- [Crow] Yeah, you don't have to
be Fellini to figure that out.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] What's the point?
- [Tom] Yeah, I bet if the
scientists sent us Citizen Kane,
it'd have a 20-minute
sled sequence in it.
- [Crow] Hey Joel,
what are these films
trying to teach us about life?
- [Joel] Well I guess
they're trying to say that
if we're born, and then we die
and there's lots of
padding in between.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Focus.
- [Crow] Oh, couldn't they
just have ordered out?
That's a long way
to go for a taco.
- [Joel] Oh, wrong place.
We better start cruising again.
(humming)
- Go for the throat.
- [Tom] Uh, maybe you should
clear your throat first.
- [Joel] Hmm, Moonfire Inn, huh?
Looks like a nice country inn,
maybe we'll see Bob Newhart.
- [Tom] Whoa!
What happened to his head?
- [Crow] Oh, Linda Blair.
- [Tom] Oh, making a ship model.
Ah men, enjoying
their manliness.
(grunting)
- [Crow] Excuse
me, that's illegal.
- Oh well, high ho.
- [Tom] What is he, a dwarf?
- Come to Little Daddy, do.
- Back off, Six Pack.
It's too early
and I'm too sober.
- [Crow] And my voice
is dubbed incorrectly.
- I'm drunk enough
for both of us.
You know I always like to
start things off with a bang.
(Tom mumbling)
- Get her, Pack!
- [Joel] Eww.
- Okay, baby.
- [Joel] I don't
mind telling you,
he looks a lot like
Gilbert Gottfried.
Huh?
- [Crow] Oh...
(imitating sad trombone music)
- I didn't see you, man.
Let me buy you a beer.
- [Tom] Uh, you just did.
- [Joel] Ah, let me get
out of some of these
wet clothes and
into a dry martini.
- [Crow] Who does
your decorating,
Paul Revere and the Raiders?
- [Joel] I'm bemused by charmed
by this plucky stranger.
- [Tom] I resent him.
- [Crow] Oh, it's a book
signing party for 150 Sex.
(chuckling)
- [Tom] Looks like Jim Garner
poked out Mariette
Hartley's eye there.
- [Joel] Hey, what's my
motivation in this scene?
Okay, got it.
- Hey you, where you from?
- [Tom] Sidehackers.
- My name's Gordon.
- That's cute, man, real cute.
- [Crow] Thank you.
- I asked you where you're from.
- I said north.
- You flying colors?
- Man, we've been
busted so many times
the only colors I fly
are exhaust black.
- I never could
run with a loser.
- [Joel] What are
we talking about?
- This is the main mama.
- You hot?
- [Tom] Aw, it's
just the humidity.
(mumbling)
- You take your old lady
on that hog and you move.
I tell the blue.
- [Crow] What the
heck are they saying?
It's like he's speaking
in an ancient tongue.
- And he said "not
here, you don't."
And he smacked me five
times on the wrist.
- [Joel] Ah, he went to a
Catholic school, probably.
(bots agreeing)
- You sound like a preacher.
(chuckling)
- Yeah, all mouth.
- [Tom] Oh, he's a pushover.
- [Crow] He's no fun,
he fell right over.
- [Tom] (chuckling) Thank you.
- [Crow] Hey, you almost
spilled my Shamrock Shake.
- You hit Daddy.
- [Joel] He hit Big Jake.
- [Tom] I've got my eye on you.
- Back off.
- [Joel] We better
back off ourselves.
Let's go, you guys.
- [Tom] What are
these people saying?
- How 'bout a couple
more beers, Lem?
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Let's see here.
Dear diary, call me Ishmael.
(chuckling) Just kidding.
Let's try that again.
Dear diary, June 10th.
This day started
strange when Crow and I
got into a fight in the
load pan bay, period.
It all started when,
unprovoked, Crow called me
a, quote, "sweatbeetle
dickweed," end quote, period.
Then all of a
sudden, he jumped me
and the next thing I
know, I was winning
when Joel discovered us.
He had to steam-hose us
off, it was a real mess,
period, paragraph there.
Damn electric typewriters.
Oh, okay, here we go.
Joel says when Crow
and I get into fights,
even if it isn't my
fault, we should remember
the good times we had together.
Like the other day, or
maybe it was last year.
Uh, before my voice changed.
Cambot, would you serve
that up for us, please?
(eerie music)
Perhaps it was two weeks ago...
- Must get back
to Galileo Seven.
Lives of 400 crew
members hang in balance!
- Vision fading.
Must cut transponder from wrist,
fashion crude phaser device
with bed slat and light bulb.
- Must control myself,
must find pastel-colored
native female.
Execute prime directive, ahhh!
(choking)
- Handsúso young-looking.
Mrs. Berg, I thought
you were Dale.
(groaning)
- Throat scratchy, hands so dry
can scratch name into--
(groaning)
- Embarrassing cuticles
on fingernails.
Must utilize emotional memory--
- Ah, listen Servo,
stop it, stop it.
- Stop?
- No, uh-uh.
- That was my big scene, Joel!
- Yeah, we were just
getting into it.
- This just isn't working.
I don't know how Shatner
does it week after week.
- I don't know why he does
it or who lets him do it.
- I think we should
just be glad he does it.
(eerie music)
Three months--
Ah, we'll be right back.
Okay, I got it.
It was a fortnight ago,
and it was a, hey, a
dark and stormy night!
(chuckling)
(instrumental theme music)
- [Joel] Hey, what were
you doing in there anyway?
- [Tom] Oh, not
much, just typing.
Cambot gave me a neat flashback.
- [Joel] Oh.
- Mama, she's got
whooping cough.
- Sick?
- [Crow] I doubt it.
- I'll take a look at her.
- Appreciate it.
- [Joel] You want
me to go right now?
I will.
Nice guy, kinda funny.
- [Tom] You know, those glasses
just don't disguise the receding
hairline there, do they?
- [Joel] He drew eyes up on top.
- [Crow] Looks like
an unsavory character.
I can't have any of that.
I'd better call Plot Stoppers.
- [Joel] Hello, angels.
- [Adrian] Good boy.
Information never hurts, Jack.
Keep 'em open.
(sultry music)
Goldie?
- [Joel] That reminds me,
I must get my watch fixed.
- [Tom] Mom!?
- How's Tahiti sound?
- Mmm.
- I thought you'd like it.
(groaning)
- [Crow] Her back looks
like a Klingon's forehead.
- Time to move on?
- [Joel] What do you call that?
- [Crow] Illegal?
- [Joel] Lunch
coming up. (gagging)
(yelling)
- [Tom] Looks like
every selection there
is Louie, Louie
except for this one.
(upbeat music)
This is the Question Mark
before the Mysterions.
♪ I go out when
the mood is right ♪
- [Joel] did you
know this cameraman
got his first job
on Midnight Special?
- [Crow] Hey, Louise Lasser.
♪ And then I take
my baby's hand ♪
- [Tom] Suzy, dead at 21.
♪ 'Cause I can't take a chance ♪
- [Joel] Kipper, sells
lightly salted meat products.
- [Crow] Six Pack, currently
working for Roseanne Barr Show.
♪ On losing my baby ♪
- [Tom] Little Sally,
girl friday to
Susan Saint James.
- [Crow] Slugger, found dead
with Coors Party Ball
lodged in throat.
- [Joel] Spazzy, broken neck
shortly after filming
of this movie.
- [Tom] Puck, co-founder of
the avant-garde dance group.
- [Crow] Iggy Pop,
we don't know why.
- [Joel] And Patches.
- [Tom] Squatter, took
a baseball in the head
in the third inning
at an Angels game.
- [Joel] Ewww!
- [Crow] I hope that's beer!
- [Tom] Yikes!
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Shields and Yarnell
working a crowd with their
famous sidewalk robot routine.
- [Tom] I can't stop doing this,
you think I like doing this?
I can't stop.
- [Crow] That was number nine!
(hooting)
- [Joel] Somebody put a wallet
under the guy's
tongue or something.
- [Tom] Bad, bad girl, naughty.
- [Crow] Timothy Hutton,
before the boat trip.
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Shagster, camouflage
expert, can hide anywhere.
And there's more, there's
Jingo and Baby Burlap
and Fleagle and Beagle
and Drooper and Snork,
and uh-oh, it's the stinky guy.
- [Tom] Drew Barrymore.
♪ I send her letters
almost every day ♪
♪ So she'll never go astray ♪
- [Crow] And aman
so mean he once
shot himself just
for snoring too loud.
♪ Make sure that
she's right at home ♪
- [Tom] Sally Kellerman!
Whoa, lookin' hot.
♪ On losin' my baby ♪
- [Crow] Well, I gotta admit it.
It does look like a fun party
♪ I can't take a chance ♪
♪ I'm losing my baby ♪
- [Joel] Hey!
Oh mama, Santa's home.
- [Crow] More, more
of the old guy!
Whoo!
♪ I don't want to
take a chance ♪
♪ To leave you behind ♪
- [Tom] There's
Trembler and Wheezer.
♪ I go out when
the moon is right ♪
- [Joel] That's sweet.
♪ And the stars are
shinin' bright ♪
- [Joel] That's so tender.
Young love.
- [Crow] Hey look,
Flo and Eddie.
- [Joel] Wow.
- [Crow] Hi and Lois.
♪ 'Cause I can't take a chance ♪
♪ I'm losing my dignity ♪
- [Tom] Everybody.
♪ No I can't take a chance ♪
- [Tom] Whoa, 3D.
♪ I'm losing my dignity ♪
(groaning)
♪ I can't take a chance ♪
♪ I'm losing my baby ♪
- [Crow] She's got really
nice skin for a junkie.
- Horny hiney.
- [Joel] Hey, it's Buck Henry.
- [Crow] Or Father Mulcahy.
(mumbling)
- Hiney...
- [Tom] Oh hey,
guys, don't eat him.
- [Woman] Horny Hiney.
- [Crow] Hey, let's cut him
in half and count the rings.
- [Tom] Yeah, these are the
Manson family home videos.
Here Tex, Squeaky and the gang
light-heartedly tease Charlie.
- [Joel] Ow, my keys
were in my back pocket.
- Humpty dumpty horny Hiney.
(all mumbling nonsense)
- Six Pack?
- [Crow] Beware of the dwarf!
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Our minds are melding.
We are becoming one.
- In the storm...
It fell overboard.
- [Crow] Because
Pepperidge Farm remembers.
- Daddy?
- [Joel] Get off my chest.
- Cube, man.
Man, you've been
out for two days.
- [Crow] No, I've
been on for two days.
- Yeah man, yeah.
- [Joel] Heavy.
- Bad trip, man.
- I don't feel so good.
- [Joel] You don't smell
so good, my compadre.
- [Tom] Better go get him
some cocaine or something.
- Mommy?
- [Joel] Oh, good
thing Cher is there
to walk the guy
around, you know?
- Everything's green.
- [Crow] That's the
inside of your eyeballs.
- [Tom] Everything's Archie.
- you'll be all right, baby.
- [Joel] Get your hair
out of my mouth...
(choking)
- Man, what a drag.
- [Crow] Ah, great
way to ruin a party.
I hate it when people OD.
(funky music)
- [Tom] I'll just blend
in with the crowd here.
Fortunately, I'm
wild on the inside.
I don't need these
hippie threads.
- [Joel] Uh, so this isn't
a meeting of the
Young Republicans?
- [Crow] Now to pick my girl.
- [Tom] So, you guys
are the Hellcats.
I'm a corporate raider.
Hi, got a card?
- [Joel] That square bugs
me, he really bugs me!
- [Tom] I'd like a room, please.
- [Crow] Hip or unhip?
I brought you here so
no one would notice.
- Tomorrow night, you're
bringing in two pounds.
- [Joel] I want it very lean,
the boss is making
Yankee pot roast.
- So it's gotta be like...
- [Tom] Like, well you know!
- Pick-up at
Scorpio's, at 12:30.
- [Tom] The drive-up window.
- Take three bikes.
- [Crow] And call
me in the morning.
- I've got the action.
- Hold it, tiger.
(seductive growling)
- When are we getting together?
- Never.
- [Crow] Great, I'm free then.
- That's no way to be.
- That is the only way to be.
- I can give you more
than these greasy bums.
- [Joel] Can you
give me body lice?
- You know what you are?
A hang-up.
- That hurts.
- Hey, pretty boy
like to fondle?
- [Tom] Hey, I'm working
on a girl right now.
I'll be right with you.
- [Crow] Better take a number.
- [Joel] I'll just
let myself out then.
(whooshing)
Sex appeal.
- [Tom] Real nice
hair on that guy.
- [Crow] This must be the
stunt cast from Room 222.
- What's that, a love letter?
- [Joel] Fan mail
from some flounder?
- I don't need your help.
- [Crow] Well you
misspelled skelter.
- [Tom] Bridget loves Bernie.
- [Crow] Bridget loves burnout.
- [Joel] There's
just something about
a girl in a flight
helmet, I don't know.
- [Crow] Hmm, Tiptoe Through
the Tulips, Five the Hard Way.
Is there anything by
Hoyt Axton on this?
- I'm not sure I can
take this much longer.
- [Tom] Oh, I hate that song.
- Just hang in there.
- [Joel] Hey, do you
like pina coladas,
getting caught in the rain?
- What's the cyclops?
- You ask me that?
Silver Cyclops of the sun-ee-ow.
The most beautiful animal
in ancient Cardiff.
Second only to a unicorn.
- Really?
- [Crow] Ross, you
gotta stop doing drugs.
- Now maybe you can
help us out (mumbling).
- I can get some Mary Jane.
- [Tom] How 'bout some pot?
- No help.
- Okay grubs, word's
in on the run.
- [Joel] Time for notes
everyone, gather round.
(shouting)
(cheering)
- [Crow] Boozefest
for everybody!
Himey, change with Bongo.
Bongo, change with Cyclops.
Cyclops, well, just change.
- [Tom] Scene's over,
that's a wrap everybody.
Thanks, lunchtime.
- [Joel] We're going
to Dairy Queen!
(cheering)
- [Crow] He was in Pippin.
(instrumental theme music)
- [Joel] Scarecrow,
check it out.
- [Tom] Uh, no Joel,
somebody's surrendering.
I think it's a--
Huh?
- [Joel] Oh, I hate to
shoot a butt like that.
- [Crow] I'll do it.
(piano music)
- [Joel] Hmm, some
surrealist homage.
Oh.
- [Tom] Steve Allen music.
- [Joel] That's probably Hummel.
- [Tom] Uh, lady,
could you please move?
You're blocking my landscape.
- [Joel] He's probably
gonna paint her,
like for Laugh-In or
something like that.
- [Crow] That's better.
- [Joel] Geez.
- [Tom] Hey, hey!
- [Joel] That's not very funny.
- [Tom] That's uncool.
- [Crow] Oh, it's
a Keane painting.
I thought the eyes are
supposed to be big.
- [Joel] Uh, I think
her skin's a number two.
- [Tom] Love the
Steve Allen music.
- [Joel] Huh?
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
Yep, that's Jesse Helms Angels.
- [Crow] Art police.
- [Tom] Give me that, I'll
show you how to use color.
- [Joel] Are you guys
working for David Hockney?
- [Crow] Hey, can we
borrow your towel?
Our bike just hit
a water buffalo.
(goofy laughing)
- [Joel] What do you think
of pointillism, creep?
- [Tom] Be on the
lookout for art gangs.
- [Crow] It's a
Benny Hill sketch.
- [Tom] Neo-realists.
- [Crow] Get away
from the poster.
- [Joel] Geez, they're too
cheap to show a location shot,
they just show a poster.
- [Tom] It's the High Times
corporate picnic
at Itchycoo Park.
- I'm so tired.
I don't think I'll
ever be the same.
- [Crow] Well don't worry,
the 60s'll be over soon.
- Beautiful, huh?
- Yeah.
- [Joel] It's all too beautiful.
(groaning)
- [Tom] Oooh.
- What's the chances of
a badge gettin' in here?
- [Tom] A badger?
Oh, are they
indigenous to the area?
- [Man] Here comes
the gut wagon!
(cheering)
- [Joel] The gut wagon?
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Joel] Looks like
the Bad Humor Truck.
- [Crow] I want a Bomb Pop.
- [Tom] I scream, you scream,
we all scream for ice cream.
- Get away!
(shouting)
Put me down!
- [Tom] They must be
out of Fintoozlers.
- [Joel] Burn the
Good Humor man,
he's out of Creamsicles!
- [Tom] Woody Woodpecker.
(imitating laughter)
Oh.
- [Crow] Ick.
(yelling)
(shouting gibberish)
- [Joel] What did he say?
- [Tom] I think he said
(shouting gibberish).
(cheerful music)
- [Joel] Wait a minute,
is this what I think it is?
- [Tom] I think it may be...
- [Crow] You're right, it's...
- [All] The bike song!
♪ This one's got an
orange gas tank ♪
♪ This one's got shiny chrome ♪
♪ This one's got all you need ♪
- [Joel] Oh, this must
be the heroin song.
- [Crow] Well, it still works.
♪ This one's filled
with speedballs ♪
♪ Heat the spoon above
the candle and shoot ♪
♪ I've seen traffic jams ♪
- [Crow] Hey, make sure
you've got plenty of
Kodak film to catch the
antics of those plucky teens.
- [Tom] How low will she go?
- [Joel] Pretty low.
♪ Mass confusion ♪
- [Crow] Mass confusion.
They're talking
about the plot, Joel.
♪ No no no no no ♪
- [All] Yes.
- [Joel] Wow, I
guess face injuries
are popular with these women.
- [Crow] They're
all piano tuners.
- [Joel] Oh.
♪ I have sailed the busy seas ♪
(blowing horn)
- [Joel] He's clearing
his spit valve.
- [Tom] Yuck.
- [Joel] Who's
drinking what there?
- [Crow] That guy's trashed.
- [Tom] Oh, he's
looking for the script.
- [Joel] Hey, he's a coaster.
♪ Mass confusion ♪
- [Crow] Hey, it's Raffi.
Thanks for the drugs.
♪ Mass confusion ♪
♪ I can't take no more of this ♪
♪ No no no no no ♪
- [All] Yes.
- [Joel] Oh, there's a
CPR class right there.
- [Tom] Tongue wrestling.
We'll turn the Metrodome
into a giant mud pit.
- [Crow] Looks
like a tongue war.
♪ All this friction,
some confliction ♪
♪ Contradiction, big election ♪
♪ Lots of things with
i-o-n at the end ♪
- [Joel] At least
they bathe, you know?
- [Tom] Look, it's
Beer Blanket Bongo.
♪ No no no no no ♪
- [All] Yes.
- Hey, Six Pack.
- [Crow] Oh, I love what
you've done with the place.
Looks so great.
- Thanks a lot.
- [Joel] These are my specimens.
- [Tom] Where do you want
to be in three years?
- [Crow] Sidehackers 2?
- [Joel] Oh, here's a
pencil in your eye--
I mean mud.
- Joy to the world,
good raineth everywhere.
(blowing horn)
Let Earth receive...
- [Joel] This is the
best Christmas ever.
(cheerful music)
- [Crow] Whoa, one more girl,
he's gonna have to juggle.
- Don't get sloshed,
you've gotta work tonight.
- Sure, sure, sure.
Anything you say, baby.
- [Tom] Hey, it's Donny Osmond.
No wonder he has so many women.
(speaking indistinctly)
(blowing horn)
- [Joel] Oh, let it lie.
- [Crow] Hey, he's
gettin' better.
- [Tom] He's doing scales.
- [Joel] Hi, funny face.
What is it, boy?
- Nowhere, man.
Everything's a big zero.
- [Tom] He must be
their accountant.
D'oh.
- [Crow] Half-nelson.
- [Tom] Sleeper hold.
- [Joel] Oh, this has been fun
but let's move the plot along.
- Peace.
- What do you mean by that?
- Like, no war.
- See you later, Monte.
- [Tom] Well, she won't
actually be seeing depth
'cause she's got one...
- [Crow] Wow, she's an eyeful.
Is she Moshe Dayan's daughter?
(imitating belching)
- tell me about it, lover.
- [Joel] Hmm? Wow.
- I just might.
So far, she's our best contact.
- Roses are green,
violets are red.
- [Joel] I like to shoot
heroin straight into my head.
- And I'm the
big-nosed bull rat.
Big-nosed bull...
- [Crow] Ipsy dipsy
Nipsey Russell.
- Hiney cubed it again.
- [Crow] Strange place
for a living room.
- [Tom] But what a view!
(engines revving)
Uh-oh.
Oh no!
- [All] Comanches!
- [Crow] And they're
riding Indians.
- [Joel] Quick,
everybody put the
living room furniture
in a circle.
- [Crow] It's the neighbors,
they've come to
borrow a cup of smack.
- [Tom] Uh hi,
we're the day shift.
Dolphin Temps sent us down.
- [Joel] I'm here for
the staring contest.
- [Crow] Oh no fair,
he's wearing glasses.
- Snakey-boy, you
having a picnic?
- Ease off, man.
- Why, Daddy?
I just wanna join
the fun and games.
- [Tom] Daddy?
- Isn't that old Sheila, baby?
- Piss off, Tommy.
- [Crow] I'm huge.
I'm not supposed
to be in this film.
They lose me after
the bunker sequence.
- Hey, Snake.
She run as good as
this little pink skate?
- Would you like to find out how
this little pink
skate runs, man?
- [Tom] Okay, what does this
have to do with anything?
- [Joel] Now, you're sure you
wanna go through with this?
(engine revving)
- [Tom] There's no turning back,
the music already started.
- [Crow] Oh wait, I
can't get mine started.
(whiny crying) Wait!
(engine revving)
- [Joel] Well, I won.
- [Tom] Bye.
So...
- [Joel] Uh-huh.
- [Tom] Well then, uh,
we'll just wait here then.
- [Joel] Friends don't let
friends drive pink motorcycles.
- [Crow] I'm completely
mesmerized by this
exciting race.
- [Joel] Yeah, we'll just wait.
We're still here, boss.
Just enjoying the race
that's over the hill.
We can't see.
(imitating squishes)
- [Tom] Eww.
- [Crow] Splat.
Eww.
- [Tom] Oh you know,
they all look like
rejects from a renaissance
festival, don't they?
(engines revving)
- [Tom] Great race.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
the Doublemint Twins.
- [Crow] One's
already been chewed.
(engines revving)
- [Tom] Whoa, that came
right out of his eye.
He must be a magician.
- [Joel] Must be a
really good race,
all that zooming
around and stuff.
- Monte, how much longer?
- Who knows?
- [Tom] Let's split, guys.
- [Joel] Ah, we
better get outta here.
How much longer is right.
- Linda, Dave was my
brother and your fiance--
- [Tom] Linda.
- We're gonna see it through.
(instrumental theme music)
- Let's see, how does
this stupid thing work?
Record and play, there we go.
Well, dear Kitty,
you won't believe
what a jerk Servo was today.
♪ La la la la ♪
Huh?
♪ Hellcats la la ♪
♪ and they got some bugs ♪
Ah, no.
(tape rewinding)
♪ Hellcats, oh yeah ♪
I'm no good with this stuff.
Let's see, hold down
record and play.
Oh, I get it, okay.
Ah, there we go.
Well, like I was saying,
you won't believe what
a jerk Servo was today.
Okay, get this,
I'm down in the load pan
bay, minding my own business
when out of nowhere,
Servo jettisons a stream
of purged wood right at
my spasmodic crofisator.
So in self-defense, and
only after every avenue
of diplomacy has been
exhausted, I jump him,
but only in self-defense.
Of course, this is the
only thing Joel sees
and I get all the blame again.
I can't blame Joel, because
finding out the truth
sometimes requires a spirited
question and answer session.
(eerie music)
Although this sounds like a
lame segue into a flashback
I remember with
particular gusto...
- Now, I'm going to be
floating some objects here.
- Uh, with wire?
- With wire, and
you're going to tell me
if they're funny
or not, all right?
First, we start off with a coat.
Funny or not funny?
- Uh...
Funny?
- Right, funny.
Next, Cambot, bring it over to
the right here a little bit.
A wrench, funny or not funny?
- Uh, I'd say funny.
- Right, funny.
Finally, a harmonica.
- Oh! Oh, oh, oh.
- Funny or not funny?
- Oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Okay, Crow, Crow.
- Um, I forgot the question.
- Funny or not funny?
- Uh, funny.
- Are you sure?
- Uh, not funny.
- It was funny, stick
to your guns Crow.
Now, I'm going to be
showing you some flashcards.
You'll be awarded 20 points
for every correct flashcard.
These are objects that are funny
or not funny when
they're floating.
All right, start
things off, sand.
- Uh, not funny.
- Right.
Okay, orange juice,
funny or not funny?
- Uh, funny.
- Right.
Next, a baseball.
- Funny.
- Wrong, not funny.
All right.
Woodchuck, funny or
not funny floating?
- Funny.
- Extremely funny.
Next, funny or not
funny floating?
Sally Fields.
- Uh, not funny.
- Right.
Next, funny or not funny
floating, Sebastian Cabot.
- Funny!
- Right, extremely
funny but impossible.
Finally, the rules get a
little blurry here, guys.
Christoper Reeves in Superman,
funny or not funny floating?
- Uh, not funny.
- Right.
Christopher Reeves in Monsignor.
- Funny.
- Right.
Now, Christopher Reeves kissing
Michael Caine in Deathtrap.
- Oh, funny!
- Right.
Finally, Gallagher, funny
or not funny floating?
- Not funny.
- Extremely unfunny.
Now, we go into the
lightning round.
Cambot, put it up on the screen
and Magic Voice, let's
have the password.
- [Magic Voice] The
secret password is,
úthings which are
funny floating.
(bell dinging)
- Uh, you take your
shoe off with this.
- A piece of cheese, a
come-along, a shoehorn.
(bell dinging)
- Right.
You keep meat in this.
- Uh, your mouth?
(bell dinging)
- Right.
Uh, a juggler.
- Boring things?
- A juggler, hackney.
- Things at a
renaissance festival.
- Bad actor.
- Things you say to a bishop.
- Pass, pass.
Thanks for the
flashback, Cambot.
Well, anyway.
That flashback had
nothing to do with
anything I was talking about.
(chuckling)
Hey, did I ever tell
you about the time
Joel dressed me
up as Judy Garland
and forced me to
sing show tunes?
I got a lotta pain.
(alarm blaring)
Oh, and I got a movie
sign all by myself!
(yelling)
(mechanical whirring)
- [Joel] Hey,
where's my tape deck?
- [Crow] Huh?
- [Joel] I said deck.
- [Crow] Oh.
(engine revving)
- [Tom] That's it then.
- [Joel] Oh, so it's not
really a skate then, is it?
- [Crow] Nope.
- [Joel] Hey!
- [Crow] Oh, I get
it, it's a triathlon.
Bike race, knife fight,
then beer guzzling.
(imitating monkeys hooting)
- [Tom] Whoa!
- [Joel] Hmm, this fight was
choreographed by Jerome Robbins.
- [Crow] A chain beats an Yves
Saint Laurent belt any time.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Joel] Pants him,
he must be pantsed.
- [Tom] I'm gonna send you
a chain letter, monkey boy.
- [Crow] It's Bob Fosse
versus Tommy Tune.
- [Tom] Both of
these competitors
really came here
to dance, folks.
Whoa.
- [Joel] They are not men.
- [Crow] These are the
chains I forged in life.
- [Joel] Looks to me like the
Battle of the Network Scum.
(angry mumbling)
- [Tom] Biker rhubarb,
biker rhubarb.
- [Joel] Bottle of
beer, bottle of beer.
- [Tom] Chain, chain,
chain of fools.
- [Joel] Subhuman,
I'm not human.
- [Crow] He's fighting
the cameraman.
Kill him!
Kill everybody!
- [Tom] The crew,
the cast, everybody.
- Peace, brothers, no more war.
- [Joel] Who is he?
(cheering)
It's Ross Hagen, the
prince of thieves.
By the time the cock
crows three times,
chili peppers will burn his gut.
Hey, your butt's dirty.
(goofy laughing)
- [Tom] I love you guys, it
don't get no better than this.
I don't know what
I was thinkin'.
- Like love, baby.
- [Joel] My work is done here.
- Over my body, baby.
- [Crow] I think
that's dead body.
[Tom] Ross...
- You losing guts, man?
- He doesn't have any.
- Don't fight him, man.
- [Tom] Come on Ross, this
is just peer pressure.
Just say no, please.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Okay, that sounds
good, my day's open.
- Hey man, it doesn't matter.
When we say drag,
we don't mean drag.
We mean, like, scrape.
- [Crow] Why don't you
just say scrape then?
- Set it up, man!
- [Tom] What's
their word for dumb?
(yelling)
Looks like a training center
for carnies, doesn't it?
- [Joel] Yeah.
Oh great, they're
gonna go oat-skiing.
- [Tom] They're gonna plow.
You know, they might
just all be Amish.
No.
- [Crow] Amish bikers?
Oh, I get it.
You take a rototiller
and you hook a guy
between the two, and
therefore avoid any plot!
I'd love to call you
later, if I'm still alive.
[Tom] I know you
love my brother,
but if you ever get lonely...
- 15 seconds, man.
If you make it,
you got no worries.
Otherwise...
- [Joel] You know...
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Joel] You just...
You know what I mean?
It's just like...
- [Tom] I'll go
put your coat back
on the bathroom floor
where it came from.
- [Crow] Well, we've
taken a pretty long lunch.
Better get it back
to the office.
Oh.
- [Tom] Maybe not.
Mm-hmm, getting the idea?
- [Joel] All right
fellas, make a wish.
- Go!
- [Tom] Oh, he
used to be a dwarf.
(engines revving)
- [Crow] Body by John Deere.
- [Joel] Obviously, kids
shouldn't try this at home
if they have rototillers.
- [Tom] Nope, kids
shouldn't try this at home.
You shouldn't be watching
this movie at home.
We're seasoned professionals.
(engines revving)
(crowd counting)
They're counting how long
he's getting in feet.
- [Crow] Oh, what a drag
but we do have some
lovely parting gifts.
- [Joel] Forward my mail!
- [Crow] I've seen dogs
do that on driveways.
- [Tom] Calgon, take me away!
(Tom humming)
- [Crow] Well, I don't know what
I was supposed to learn by that.
- [Tom] What a day to forget
my metal boxer shorts.
- [Joel] It's the
Ross Hagen actor pull
with Gogo the Gorilla
dragged behind a motorcycle.
- [Crow] Oh no, he's
backing up, how horrible!
(groaning)
- [Tom] Oh my lord,
it's just his legs!
(crying)
- [Joel] He's gone.
- [Tom] Oh no.
Doesn't anybody care?
What's the matter with you?
The only one concerned
is the music.
- [Crow] Oh great, Ross.
Yeah, take your jacket off.
You wouldn't want anything
thick and leathery
between you and the road.
- [Joel] He's bright.
- [Tom] Except maybe his head.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Joel] You know, guys,
this didn't have much success
as an Olympic event, but it
is in the Goodwill Games.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Joel] He made it.
- [Tom] Think his
medical covers this?
- [Crow] Uh, that one's
loose, you wanna tighten that?
- [Joel] Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Dirt Row.
Please direct your
eyes to center stage
where daredevil stuntman
actor Ross Hagen
is about to attempt a
most dangerous stunt.
To imagine what
he's going through,
picture yourself
attached to over 500
wild horses being stretched.
- [Crow] If you
think this is easy,
try holding your breath for
the duration of this stunt.
- [Tom] Oh, I've seen a
man pulled clean in half
last week's state
fair in Florida.
(crowd counting)
- [Joel] Oh, this is
to stretch his arms
so he looks more Neanderthal.
(chuckling)
Oh, for fun.
- [Tom] Yep, 15
feet, four inches.
- [Crow] Ah, the
sun was in my eyes.
- [Tom] They stretched my
legs out, they snagged on me.
It's all hot and
it hurts and stuff.
- [Crow] Well, same
thing tomorrow?
Now Ross can put the
star on the tree.
- [Joel] Yeah.
We're gonna have to let
your sleeves out, Ross.
(bikers talking)
- [Tom] I'm just gonna
stretch out here on the couch.
- [Crow] Home again,
home again, jiggity jig.
- [Joel] I love
him, he's so dumb.
- [Tom] They need to give
him a beer, a longneck.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] Yeah, now he's
really a long arm of the law.
(laughing)
(sultry music)
Congratulations, you are
now officially white trash.
- Now you said it, baby,
that's what I want.
Come on, eight and
ten here, come on!
- [Tom] Whee-hoo.
No jumping on the furniture.
Come on, don't mess
up the living room.
- You can't do it here!
- [Joel] Yeah, not in front
of all these hoodlums.
- [Crow] That's
my man's brother.
- [Tom] Oh, the
love and the fun.
You know, it's just
like that scene
from It's A Wonderful Life.
Hey, hurry up with that blanket.
George Bailey don't wanna be
lookin' at no busted bedsprings.
- We all gotta go sometime.
Will it hurt?
- [Crow] Not if you do it right.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Hey, check it out.
That guy's a number 13.
(cheering)
- There just wasn't
anything left.
(indistinct shouting)
- [Tom] You kids go off to bed,
your mother and I are busy.
- [Joel] You know, this
is how my mom and dad met.
I'm just kidding.
- [Crow] Nummy nummy
nummy, I'm eating you up!
Nummy nummy nummy.
Num num.
(sultry music)
- [Tom] Time to go undercover.
- [Crow] Does this
mean that you have to
do something really
stupid to get the girl?
- [Tom] Yep.
- [Joel] I'm a little rabbit.
(goofy laughing)
- Little mama.
You're too yummy
to be alone here.
- [Tom] Yeah, she
comes in six flavors.
- What do you say we
make tracks? (mumbling)
- [Joel] Tractor mortars?
- No need to act like that.
- [Crow] Yak like what?
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Pablum?
Pottery wheel?
- He can help you.
- [Joel] Pottery wig?
Oh, young love.
- [Crow] Oh, there's
his pottery wheel
and there's his tractor motor.
- [Joel] Oh, he was
actually saying that.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] And his Pablum.
Huh, a human tooth.
Huh, neat.
- [Crow] (gagging) The
nerves are attached still.
(gagging)
- [Joel] Never give a woman a
human molar on a first date.
- [Tom] Nice pants.
- [Crow] Creepy girl.
- [Tom] Hey, whoa!
Diana Rigg taught her that.
Thank you, Emma Peel.
(laughing)
- [Crow] Oh good,
the paramedics.
And they took CPR
from Anheuser-Busch!
- [Joel] Mmm, love is good.
You taste like chili peppers.
- Who was that dude
bugging you last night?
= [Tom] That was you!
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- I thought you went with me.
- Off and on.
- Mostly on or mostly off?
- You're mostly curious.
- [Joel] It's mostly magic.
- A lot to be curious about.
Like that map of Mexico.
- Monte, baby I love you
but you ask too many questions.
- [Crow] He watches
a lot of Jeopardy.
- My mind's like a sponge.
- [Tom] You can
clean a sink with it.
- They don't want
to bother you much.
- [Joel] Mmm!
(blubbering)
- [Crow] I hope that's beer.
- [Joel] Exactly.
- [Crow] Hey,
Adolph's found a girl.
I think her name is Eva.
- [Tom] No, it's Annie Lennox.
- [Crow] All the
Hellcats in Whoville,
they spanked their denfanklers,
they blew their fintoozlers
and cranked their graflanklers.
- [Tom] They whizzed
their gizfunklers
and shanked their whisthanklers,
they toozled and woozled
and peanuted kirktanklers.
- [Crow] Even little
Wendy Lou Hellcat.
- [Tom] Went through.
- Hi.
- [Joel] My jaw hurts.
- [Tom] Don't ask.
- I hope you had fun.
- Duty, kid, duty.
- [Joel] Double duty.
- Seeing as how you were locked
in combat with the enemy,
I got to Scab for this.
- [Joel] You got a scab in here?
- [Tom] Gross.
- [Joel] Eww, what'd
you say that for?
That's so disgusting.
(mumbling)
- [Crow] So I was just saying,
chili peppers burn my gut.
- They tell me you fooled Scab.
- So?
- So that's good.
You ride this Wednesday.
I want you to come
with me tonight.
- [Tom] She asked
me, she asked me!
- Rita's bombed out
and I need a rider.
- I'm ready.
I'm not too fond of the
company around here anyway.
- [Joel] Wait, what are you--
Oh yeah, you don't like me.
- [Tom] Pardon my
boardinghouse reach.
(goofy laughing)
- [Crow] Bozo's so funny.
No clothes on, I could
look at it forever.
(goofy laughing)
- [Joel] Hmm, I see you're
using the King's Indian defense
against my classical
variation, I see.
- [Tom] Here's Lee Meriwether
in her first starring role.
(groaning)
- [Joel] I think that's
her first camisole too.
- Please?
- [Joel] Please stop the guitar
playing, I hate flamenco!
(groaning)
- [Crow] Football practice.
- [Tom] Uh-huh...
- [Woman] Please, please...
- [Tom] All done?
- Please...
- [Tom] Wonder what she wants.
- [Crow] Why castle when you
could get a queen's pawn?
- [Joel] Could you please
play Yahtzee for a change!?
- Pete...
- [Tom] Can I please
use the bathroom?
- [Joel] No, come on, you know
this is only the sixth day.
(groaning)
- [Crow] Now look,
there's a chicken pot pie
in the fridge but I'm not gonna
get you a Libbyland dinner.
- Nothing in life is free.
- [Crow] Only the best things.
- [Tom] Hey, how
come these loser guys
always get these
really great leg holds?
You're pretty good, Karpov.
- [Crow] Yeah,
you too, Kasperov.
- [Joel] Charro, knock it off!
- [Crow] You know, I can
see why she loves him.
- [Tom] You know,
mixing dice with chess
really speeds up
the game, Karpov.
(engines rumbling)
- [Joel] Maybe she just
wants a glass of water.
Ah, that must be
grandma, I'll get it.
- [Crow] Get me a Dove
bar, and some smack.
- [Tom] Looks like they're being
visited by a constellation.
- [Crow] It's Orion.
- [Tom] Ore-Ida?
- [Crow] You're late,
I burned supper.
(engines rumbling)
- [Joel] Ah, hola, el trasho.
- Make it fast, we're late.
- [Crow] I know a wiener
man, he owns a hot dog stand.
There.
- Ah, I haven't met you.
- [Tom] I haven't
met you either.
That would leave me one up.
- I like blondes.
- Look, but don't touch.
(awkward laughter)
- A fireball, eh?
Hey Pete, look what we got here.
- [Joel] Huh, looks
like a fireball.
- Nice.
- Back off slob,
this isn't a game.
We're here to make a pick-up,
not act as entertainment
for you crumbs.
- [Crow] Ah, here's
the entertainment.
- Get closer...
Help me out, will you?
- [Tom] I just don't
get algebra, man.
- [Joel] I need some thread
and an egg and a wheat penny.
- [Crow] No, no, don't make
her watch Cop Rock again!
- [Tom] Come on, it's actually
gotten some good reviews.
(woman crying)
- [Joel] Uh, she's been sick.
- [Woman] Oh Pete...
- [Crow] Here, divinity.
Made it myself.
- [Joel] But, but...
Butt?
- [Crow] You get your
hand stamped in this gang
so if you leave,
you can get back in.
- [Tom] Great music.
- If I don't see you again,
you can be sure I
won't forget you.
- [Tom] Your wind
song stays on my mind.
- The smell won't wash off.
- [Joel] Uh, so I guess a second
date's out of the question?
(engines revving)
- [Crow] Wish I'd said that.
- [Tom] Stella!
- [Joel] Now, let's see about
getting that young
lady some heroin.
(engine rumbling)
- [Crow] I said, I
know a wiener man!
Oh, forget it.
- [Tom] He owns a hot dog stand?
- [Joel] He gives me everything.
- [Tom] Oh my god, wait
til Andy hears about this.
We're gonna have to
nip it in the bud.
- One Adam-12, One
Adam-12, see the bike.
(mumbling)
(siren wailing)
What, are we watching this from
the Flubber-cam all of a sudden?
I don't get this.
- [Tom] Whoa!
(tires screeching)
- [Crow] And that's why kids
should not have mini-bikes.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
News flash, biker
wipes out, film at 11.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Eyewitness News Break.
Ah, she smeared her makeup.
What a mess.
(instrumental theme music)
- [Crow] Oh, not the clown
suit reference again,
not for four times in a row~
(humming)
- [Tom] Honey, I'm dead!
- Where's Betty?
- I don't know, did
you have any trouble?
- No.
- [Joel] Was this film
recorded on 78 RPM?
- Just heard it
on the car radio.
- [Joel] Wayland
Flowers is dead.
(mumbling)
- We got problems.
- [Crow] I can see you're
all busted up inside.
- [Tom] Hello, I'd like
to send a Candy Cave-gram.
(phone ringing)
- [Crow] They've dialed
into What's My Line.
Is he known for his
work in the theater?
- [Joel] No, I don't
wanna buy any light bulbs.
- I don't care how.
- [Tom] You must
sink the Bismark.
- [Crow] He must live
in a target sales area.
- [Joel] He's a
Flintstone kid, too.
He's taking vitamins.
- We've gotta get her stash.
- She's got a mustache?
They're gonna have to use
hot wax to get that off.
- [Crow] Ouch.
Sad times befall the
scum of the earth.
When bad things
happen to bad people.
- [Tom] Why is he so sad?
Come on, there's gotta
be more pot-bellied
sag-breasted scum
of the earth with
butts like leather
pancakes for him to love.
- No, no, no!
- [Crow] No, n-no no, no.
- Take it easy, Hiney.
Easy, man.
- [Crow] She had my stash.
(crying)
- We gotta go into
Holdstone and get her load.
- But how?
(mumbling)
- Find out.
Now make it.
- [Joel] Make it happen,
be a self-starter, come on.
Your bike is.
(engine starting)
well she's back there then.
- [Tom] Bye.
- [Crow] Bye.
(screaming)
- [Joel] She's on the bike.
- [Tom] Uh-oh, she's
riding a black tarry BMW.
(engine rumbling)
- [Tom] Hi.
- [Joel] Yeah, put his
head back on, I gotta go.
- [Tom] Well, at least
we have each other.
Oh!
(engine rumbling)
- [Crow] They look as confused
by the film as we are.
- [Joel] Well, the old
clock on the wall says
it's time for jokes,
riddles and more
with Kooky the
Motorcycling Clown.
(humming)
- [Tom] The oboe
represents this slag heap.
- [Joel] Let's watch as that
disaster-prone do-it-yourselfer
gets into his usual
batch of mischief.
(shouting)
(humming)
- [Tom] Hmm, what gives?
- [Joel] Kooky's got a plan,
and this is part of it.
- [Tom] The old junkyard.
Oh I get it, and so does Kooky.
(humming)
Kooky's in the clear, or is he?
- [Joel] We think the
joke will be on Kooky.
- [Crow] Uh-huh.
- [Joel] There it is...
And there they are.
(groaning)
(laughing)
Oh, that Kooky.
- [Tom] Oh, Kooky,
you've done it again.
- Those mothers.
Such a simple thing
and they blow it.
- [Tom] Now read
that back to me.
- We better wrap this up.
- [Crow] Please do, right now.
Let's get some paint
and paint The End.
- Don't tell your mother
where we're going, idiot!
- I didn't mean
to tell my mother.
- [Tom] You and your
daughter are doomed.
- I didn't do anything
wrong, honest.
- [Joel] Uh-oh, Kooky's
in trouble, as usual.
- they asked me to get
something out of the headlights.
- [Crow] Kooky,
your mother and I
are very disappointed in you.
(engine rumbling)
- [Tom] Meanwhile, in
a Barbara Feldon movie.
- [Crow] Would you
believe Barbara Eden?
How about Barbara Bel Geddes?
- [Joel] In The Nude Bomb.
Sounds kinda like music from
Playboy After Dark,
that old show.
- [Tom] There's a
Mingus quality to it.
- [Crow] Okay, you're riding
your bike, we get the point.
- [Tom] Oh great, and there's
another guy riding a bike.
We get the point!
- [Crow] Oh, is she
still riding her bike?
Good, for a minute I
was afraid the director
wasn't gonna make
that clear enough!
- [Tom] And still
riding her bike.
Hey, it's a drive-through.
(shouting)
Hey, look over here.
Hi, sexy.
- [Joel] Hey, come
on, leave her alone.
- [Tom] It's a fireplug, sorry.
(humming)
- [Joel] Thought
you might need help
padding out the last
10 minutes od the film.
- Just want to make
sure I get my share.
- What's the matter,
don't you trust me?
- As a matter of fact, no.
- [Crow] As a matter
of fact, who cares
what happens in
this stupid movie?
(humming)
(imitating horns)
- [Tom] Kinda like
Courageous Cat music.
(humming)
Whoa.
- [Joel] Nice office.
- She followed me.
- I'm gonna carve you...
- [Crow] Hey, we shake
hands in this country, pal.
- Tie her in the shop.
- [Joel] Force her
to watch Cop Rock.
- [Crow] Wow, that guy is mean.
- [Tom] Well, send in
the next applicant.
- Go pack.
Now!
- [Tom] Is that
her name, Go Pack?
- [Crow] She's Chinese.
- [Joel] Ooh, that was close.
Last time he was like this,
he made me watch Doogie Howser.
- [Crow] So, what
qualifications do
you feel you can
bring to our company?
- Just curious?
- Again?
(screaming)
- [Tom] Wow, she's a
good ventriloquist.
- Don't worry.
- [Crow] This week
at Sir Laughs-A-Lot,
undercover biker
chick and Boddy!
- [Joel] The hair is protein.
Using Protein-21
religiously helps put back
some of the protein
shampoo takes out.
- [Tom] He likes
me, he really...
- [Crow] I move
among the shadows.
In the daytime, I'm Ross Hagen.
We'll be right back.
- [Tom] Thrill, as Rommel tries
in vain to find the entrance.
- [Joel] Poorly designed
buildings burn my gut.
(grumbling)
Hey, is there a
receptionist here?
Do I need an appointment?
- [Tom] Looks like a
soundstage with paneling.
- [Joel] There's no
ceiling to speak of.
- [Tom] Whoa, focus.
- [Crow] Focus, focus!
- [Tom] Oh, I'm tripping.
(knocking)
- Come in.
- [Crow] While Dad's not
looking, Kooky tokes up.
That Kooky, what a character.
- This is your court-appointed
lawyer, Mr. Garber.
- Have you been
informed of your rights?
- [Joel] Hey, don't give
into the man, Kooky!
- Have you or haven't you?
- [Tom] Only Kooky's
hairdresser knows for sure.
- [Sheriff] Dick!
- Did you call me, Sheriff?
- [Joel] No, I called you Dick.
- Escort Mr. Jay Dalton
Collins the Third
to his quarters so he
can consult with counsel.
- [Tom] Kooky, have you
been putting on airs again?
Well, ha ha, that's
our Kooky, hee hee.
(playing trumpet)
- [Crow] It's King
Richard, inviting you
to the renaissance
festival, huzzah!
- [Tom] Hang down your
head, Dumb Dooley.
- [Joel] You know, he's really
multi-layered for a villain.
(humming vaudeville music)
♪ Your chick was killed,
your chick was killed ♪
- Man, like,
somebody's gonna pay.
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm not gonna
pay for the whole keg myself.
I swore I'd never.
- You with me, Pack?
- I don't know, Hiney.
It can happen, man, to anybody.
- But it didn't, it
happened to Betty.
And some little
scum's gonna pay.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Okay, dearest Sandy,
well, those bots
are at it again.
I just finished cleaning up
their mess in the commissary,
then find out that
those knuckle-knobs
had trashed the load pan
bay, exclamation point.
Sometimes I wish I had
programmed more maturity
into their little ROMs,
but you know, Sandy,
they can be the cutest
little Dickinses
in spite of themselves,
smiley face.
Well, like the time
we all got together
and learned a little bit
more about, well, you'll see.
(eerie music)
Cambot, let's have it.
- We'll just sit here and act as
the brunt of your
little visual joke?
- Yeah, that's right,
something like that.
Okay, this one is
called the binocular.
- Hey, get us, we're a
piece of stock footage.
- All right, and this
one is the keyhole-scope.
- Oh, you're the only
man for me, Servo.
- All right, this is the
high-powered scope-scope.
(whistling La Marseillaise)
- And so the French
Prime Minister shall
receive the Quadr--
Look out, look out!
- Okay, this is the
periscope-scope.
- I don't care how you do it,
you must sink the Bismark.
- [Joel] And also the
Driving Miss Daisy-scope.
- We might as well be walkin'
as driving this
slow, Miss Daisy.
- Just watch where you're going.
- Okay, this here
is the micro-scope.
- Uh, go ahead Crow,
you can imitate
a one-celled animal
better than I can.
- I am an ameba.
- [Joel] Kind looks
a bit more like the
Sammy Davis Jr.-scope.
- Oh yeah.
♪ The candyman ♪
- This is the Lucy-scope.
- Ah, Ricky!
Turns out I was never funny.
- Okay, the small
intestine-scope.
- Oh, I feel so funky.
I need soothing and coating.
- This is the Jose
Feliciano-scope there.
- [Crow] Chico, don't
get discouraged!
- All right, this is
the Family Circus-scope.
- Okay, who broke my vase?
- Not me!
(chuckling)
- Okay, followed by
the Jack O'Lantern-scope.
- Huh?
- The glaucoma-scope.
- [Bots] What?
- And if you wanna get
really fancy, you add
the Family Circus-scope
with the glaucoma-scope
and get the Hubble-scope.
Okay, there's that.
- [Bots] Ooh.
- Followed by the Pope-scope.
- Huh?
- The Scopes monkey trial-scope,
otherwise known as
Inherit the Wind-o-rama,
the ever popular nope-scope.
- Oh brother!
- Oh, for fun.
Turn around and they are young.
Turn around and they've grown.
Turn around and
they are old bots
with young bots of their own.
Your friend in
space, Joel Robinson.
Commercial sign.
(instrumental theme music)
(slapping)
- [Joel] Oh man.
- [Tom] Guess this means Ross
doesn't get the job, huh?
- [Crow] Ouch.
[Joel] Next time, I connect.
- You can't expect us to believe
you just happened by
here, now, can you?
- [Tom] 'Cause if you tell
us that, we'll believe you.
- I think I'm going to have
to question your young lady.
Stridently.
- Slob.
- [Tom] Good read.
- [Joel] That's Mr. Slob to you!
(screaming)
(crying)
- [Crow] Now like I
was saying, it's a
caring, nurturing
relationship I'm looking for.
(rattling)
- [Crow] Well he's got
a thing or two to learn
about tying people to furniture.
(chuckling)
- [Tom] We heard about
your kneecaps, Ross,
and we don't want
you to get away.
- [Joel] Hey, hey, it's me.
The guy from--
the girl from the mattress.
(mumbles)
- [Crow] Huh, you talkin' to me?
- Man, you didn't ell me
how much pull they'd have.
- I wanted a surprise.
- [Joel] I'm surprised.
- Monte, are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Why did you follow?
- [Crow] I'm falling
in love with your bike.
- Incurable stupidity.
- Let's get this
place cleaned out.
- [Joel] That means you leave.
- [Tom] Here, eat these.
- I'll have the
boat ready at 4:00.
Here's the apartment key.
- [Crow] Tell Jack Lemmon and
Shirley Maclaine I want 'em out!
(mumbles)
- We have to take care of him.
- There's plenty of
room in the harbor.
- [Joel] They're big people.
- Call Jack and tell him to
keep an eye on Sheila's punch.
- [Tom] Who's Jack and Sheila?
- [Crow] I don't know.
- How would you like
to go to Tahiti?
- [Crow] That'd be great!ú
- I've just decided to
sign a full statement.
- [Tom] to his podiatrist?
- [Sheriff] No
pressure, no coercion?
- No sir, just trying
to pay back the takers.
- [Tom] Boy, not even Kooky
knows what that means.
- [Joel] These cuts are
making my pulse race.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Can I talk to you?
- [Crow] Now this is
an ordinary wooden box.
- Are you sure?
- Out.
- [Joel] Are you sure?
- [Tom] Out!
(door slamming)
Thank you.
- I can't hack this dungeon.
So why don't you untie
me and pass the soap?
- Talk first.
- I don't like being roughed up.
- [Tom] Or overexposed.
- You want action,
that's okay by me.
You pay, I play.
- [Crow] Oh, a pool player huh?
- [Joel] Will you take a check?
- [Crow] Oh my god,
his head's gone!
- [Tom] If only I could
get to my utility belt.
Batgirl!
- [Joel] Oh thank
goodness, they found
a Dremel tool with
a cutting blade.
- [Crow] Whew.
- [Tom] Amazing.
What a coincidence!
- [Crow] Oh, but
it's three-pronged
and they've got no adapter!
Oh, I see.
- [Tom] Just reach...
Thank goodness she grounded it.
- [Joel] Now, I'm gonna have to
cut your hand off,
so it might hurt.
Which one do you write with?
(whirring)
- [Tom] Oh, oh,
that was my tendon!
That's okay, thanks.
- [Crow] Hah, take that!
And this, and a little of that!
- [Tom] Oh, oh. Huh?
- [Joel] Ah, one of those huh?
No bullets, though.
- [Tom] Still think I'm fat?
- [Crow] I gotta get outta here.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
I wish I had that bra now!
- [Joel] So she ran, and she ran
and she ran and she ran.
They got it all on film.
- [Tom] Good stuff.
(imitating background music)
- [Crow] Quick, call Gab-teen!
(phone ringing)
- [Tom] Give me that!
Hello, this is Gab-teen.
- [Joel] Uh, speak
up, I can't hear you.
- Hang in there, mama.
We're on our way.
- [Crow] We're on our way!
- Okay troops.
You got your wish, Hiney.
Let's rumble!
- [Tom] Let's go, teen gang!
(shouting)
huh?
- [Crow] Uh-oh.
- Okay, what's the action?
Drop the steel.
Puck?
- the action is, old
Lump here is a crate spy.
- [Joel] A corn spy?
I've been called a lot
of things in my life,
but never a corn spy!
- [Crow] If she could
only get back to her...
Ah...
Bat-whip!
- [Tom] Well, I'd
say this movie is
starting not to make any sense.
(yelling)
- [Crow] I got
sucked right into it
and now I don't know
what's going on.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Hey, have some
potassium in your diet.
- [Crow] Recess everybody!
(cheering)
Ah, stings!
(engines starting)
Hey Joel, did you ride
your bike to school?
- [Joel] Yeah, I did.
- [Tom] They're
excited aren't they?
Bye.
Hello.
It's Don Ho's sister Heidi.
Later we'll meet
his brother Heave.
(chuckling) Ow.
You could get injured that way.
- [Crow] What's going on?
- [Tom] I don't know.
I'm lost!
- [Crow] And so is she.
Not a thought in her
tiny little brain.
- [Joel] Oh, looks like
she's into safe walking.
- [Tom] How do these work?
- [Crow] Putting
on her jimmy shoes.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Tom] Jimmy socks.
Uh, ma'am, I believe
this is my hotel room.
(whistling)
Sounds like travelogue music.
- [Joel] This is how
we say hello in Tahiti.
- [Tom] Whoa!
- [Crow] There's some beer
in the fridge for you.
- [Tom] Focus, please?
Cut, and print it.
Beautiful, people, that's good.
Let's break for
drugs, uh, lunch.
- [Joel] Here's
your Gideon bible.
(engines rumbling)
- [Tom] 300 CCs of
high-test padding!
More Mingus music.
Lean into it.
- Let's move it.
- [Crow] Like you've never
moved before, even slower!
- [Tom] Love the attention
to detail on the sets.
Oh brother.
You know, a new musical
style is introduced
every five minutes in this film.
- [Crow] I'm sorry
the car's such a mess,
I kinda live out of it.
Just throw that
stuff in the back.
Move that sweater.
(instrumental theme music)
- [Tom] Now then,
for Ross's next trick
he'll be tied up securely
and he'll be immersed in
the chilly Atlantic waters.
Let's watch.
- [Crow] Ooh, ouch.
- [Tom] And he'll
be knocked out.
(slapping)
- [Joel] If you think this is
easy, try holding your breath
for the amount of time Ross
and his pal are underwater.
- [Crow] Packed in
their own juices.
- [Tom] Now, 12 pounds of
rope are used to secure them.
(engines revving)
- [Joel] You know,
I never get tired
of seeing bikers on the highway.
- [Tom] No, neither do I.
This is what this
movie's all about.
- Eddie!
Eddie!
- [Tom] Penny?
- Hook it up to the scow
and let's get outta here.
- [Crow] Yeah, hitch
your pony to a star.
- [Tom] Oh my god,
it's Aunt Bea!
- [Crow] Hey, Aunt
Bea's lookin' fine.
- [Tom] Now, oh, it's not.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Think she would've
hurled pickles at
'em or something.
- How much longer, Eddie?
- Five minutes, Mr. Adrian.
- [Joel] Hey, that's
kinda personal.
- [Tom] Where'd he come from?
- You sure took your sweet time.
- [Tom] Thank you.
- Come on.
- [Crow] Hey, they're
in a different city now!
- [Tom] What's going on?
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Joel] Hey, Aunt Bea's here,
there's gonna be a rumble.
- [Tom] We'll get 'em.
Okay, now why are they here?
To get revenge for the girl?
- [Crow] No, she
died in an accident.
- [Joel] They're here
to save their friends
is what's going on.
- [Tom] Ooh.
Altruism, interesting.
Did he have to park that there?
- [Crow] Hey, throw that
extension cord in the water.
- [Joel] 'Scuse us,
gotta do a rumble.
- [Tom] Yeah, we'll be
outta the way in a minute.
= [Joel] 'Scuse us.
- [Crow] Coming through.
- [Joel] Sorry.
- [Tom] Sorry to
shake your camera.
Hope we're not in the shot.
(humming dramatic music)
Come on, teen gang!
- [Crow] Monkey pile!
- [Joel] Monkey
pile on the fat guy!
Hey please, kids, take it easy.
I'm reading for a Jack
Weston-type role tomorrow.
(imitating music)
- [Tom] whoo-hoo!
- [Joel] Still fast!
Aw, come on kids,
Dad's gotta go to work.
(imitating music)
- [Tom] Whoo-hoo.
Looks like fun.
- [Crow] Okay, you hit me.
You made your point,
there's no sense in--
ow, wait.
- [Joel] So they
woozled their funklers
and wonked on their fooklers.
- [Crow] They blew
their gizwanklers
and mooshed their kinflanklers.
They beat on his kidneys
and turned them to mush.
They pounded his brain
and it started to gush.
- [Tom] Hey get my hat outta
there, it's in there somewhere.
- [Joel] And Ross is free!
(cheering)
he's broken a new world
record for boredom!
- [Tom] Hey, kill that
guy, he's the director!
Get him!
- [Joel] You know guys,
this kinda reminds ms,
I've been on a
seafood diet lately.
- [Tom] Oh really?
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm
eating a lot of fish
and shrimp and stuff like that.
- [Tom] That's great.
Feel good?
- [Joel] He's probably trying to
direct this as he's
running, you know?
- [Tom] Yep, yep.
- [Crow] All right,
track along with me.
Now pan up.
Okay, get me in the car.
We'll do a cutaway.
- [Joel] Put it in park
pal, you're coming with me.
- [Tom] Oh hey,
he really hit him.
He's never gonna
hire Ross again.
- [Crow] I'll give you
an emotional memory!
- [Tom] Whoa.
- [Joel] That's for
putting me in the movie!
Ah, for fun.
I'm tired.
(sirens wailing)
But it's a good kinda tired.
- [Crow] Finally, the cops.
- [Tom] Ah-hah, so it was the
disposal barge all along.
- [Joel] Ooh.
- [Crow] I get it.
- I know what you mean.
Sure, I'll tell them.
No, I gotta get back.
- [Crow] I've got
a war to fight.
- Okay, thanks for calling.
- [Tom] No, thank you.
- What was it?
- [Joel] That was my brother.
Turns out he never died.
(snickering)
- I'm sorry.
- Old Moon Goose came
out with the whole story.
- [Tom] Muumuus?
- So things might not
go too bad with them.
- I hope so.
- Me too.
- [Tom] Yeah, we
had a lot of laughs.
- [Joel] Well, it's been fun.
- [Crow] Say, I like
the new Barbiemobile.
- [Tom] Well, I guess that's it.
Let me know if
you're gonna marry
another one of my brothers.
- Give my love to your folks.
- [Crow] They're dead,
they were killed by bikers.
- When do you leave?
- Tomorrow.
I have to sign some depositions
and things in the morning.
- [Joel] And they're going
to film every minute of it.
- [Monte] Mama, be good.
- [Tom] Be very good.
- You too, papa.
- [Joel] Huh?
- Hey, what are you
gonna do with that thing?
- [Crow] Thought I'd
make a lamp out of it.
- Keep it.
I like it.
- [Tom] I like this bike.
(engine rumbling)
(upbeat music)
- [Joel] Hey.
Hear that?
It's the bike song.
(whistling)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] It was the bike song.
♪ Into a Hellcats way
of life they lead ♪
(humming gibberish)
- [Tom] Wish I had a tambourine.
Everybody now!
♪ Hellcats in little
wooly things ♪
♪ Hellcats ♪
(singing gibberish)
♪ Upside down ♪
♪ When they get in
a dressing gown ♪
♪ Hellcats ♪
♪ Wearing Holsted ensembles ♪
♪ Losing all their marbles ♪
♪ Hellcats ♪
- [Crow] The end.
- [Tom] Okay.
Oh no, they're gonna
start it over again?
No, we're not gonna
sit through this twice.
I'm sorry.
- [Joel] Let's go.
- [Tom] Let's
blow, I don't care.
- [Joel] Ah, lift you up.
- [Tom] Thank you.
Groovy music, though.
(machanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Dear Richard, how are you?
I am fine.
Everyone's sad but me.
Dear Richard, how are you?
- Whatcha working on, pumpkin?
- Diary.
- Oh, she's working
on a diary you guys.
Hey, honey, you gotta
type into the thing
for the words to come
out on the paper.
- Paper.
- Diary.
Hey, what do you wanna keep
a diary for, you big femme?
- Ooh.
- Yeah, hey, only
ninnies keep diaries.
- Oooh.
- Ninny.
- Femme.
- You guys, that's not fair.
You know, I keep a diary.
- Really?
- Diary.
- Yeah, I do.
It's a good way to keep from
making mistakes in the future.
You know, see what
you lived through.
Kinda like what Neitzsche
says, eternal recurrence.
- Of the structures and stuff.
- Ah well, I admit it,
I keep a diary too.
- Yay!
- But only of cool stuff
that happened to me.
- Yeah, me too.
- Huh?
- What?
- Me too, okay, I
keep a diary too!
- All right, come here you guys.
- Awww!
- See?
- Hey Joel, what are you all
of a sudden, Dick Van Patten?
(laughing)
- Let's can this corn
and read a letter,
you big mushwads.
- Letters!
- All right, this one is to
everyone on the Satellite
of Love, let's put that
up on still-store, Cambot.
Thought you might like to know
that you have fans in Italy.
- Oh.
- Pretty cool.
- Through the insight and
effort of our friend Chad
in Dallas, we receive
recordings of MST3K.
It is a brilliant
switch from Italian TV.
- I'll say.
- Some of whose
programs might one day
be forced upon you
in an experiment.
- Oh, yikes.
- If you're ever in the
neighborhood, drop in.
Arrivederci, Jacqueline McNulty.
- Linguini.
- Hiroshima, mon amour.
- Come on you guys, we've
had a pretty good day.
- Oh, I love you guys.
- Come here Crow, come here.
- Ah, ow, ow.
(crying)
- I think I am going to vomit.
That is the most
disgusting display
of emotion I have ever seen.
Get us out of this
nightmare, Frank.
(crying)
- Oh the pathos.
The joy.
Why can't we know love
the way they know love!?
- Would you push
the button please?
- Come on, give me a
hug you big galoot.
- Would you get away from me?
- Come on, work the steps
Doctor, give me a big hug.
- You know, Frank...
Now you've got me doing it.
- What's so bad
about feeling good?
(crying)
- Let's push the
button together.
(slow theme music)
(shouting gibberish)